A Finding Aid to the Chuck and Jan Rosenak Research Material, circa 1938-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.rosechuc
Archives of American Art
- Research Files, circa 1938 -1999; Series 1; (Boxes 1-9, 19; 9.2 linear ft.)
  - Contemporary American Folk Art: A Collector's Guide, circa 1952-1997; 1.3
    - Hamilton, Ray, circa 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Harvey, John, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Hawkes, Gerald, circa 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Homeless Artists, circa 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Howell, Robert, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hrovat, Joe, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hudson, Sylvanus, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hunter, Reverend John ("J. L"), circa 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray, circa 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Isik, Levent, circa 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Anderson, circa 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Clyde, circa 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Jones, M. C. ("Five Cent"), circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Kass, Jacob, circa 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Keller, Allan, circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Kendrick, Eddie Lee, circa 1977-1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Kennedy, Leon, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Kinney, Charley and Noah, circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Kinney, Hazel, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Komer, Ray, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Le Ravin, Reverend Mary, circa 1991- 1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lewis, Tim, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ludwiczak, Theodore ("Ted"), circa 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - MacKay, Oscar, circa 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
    - Mackintosh, Dwight, circa 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Mason, John R., circa 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Materson, Raymond, circa 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Mayora, Sergio, circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - McGriff, Columbus ("Dude"), circa 1991 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - McMillan, Sam, circa 1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - McNeillis, Laura Craig, circa 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Merrill, Mary Francis, circa 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Milestone, Mark Casey, circa 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Miller, Reuben ("R. A."), circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Mitchell, Reggie, circa 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Moore, Deacon Eddie, circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Mulligan, Mark Anthony, circa 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Nathenson, Jamie, circa 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Orth, Kevin, circa 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Pardee Collection, Iowa City, IA, circa 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Patterson, Donald, circa 1994 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Pelner, Greg, circa 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Philpot, David, circa 1984-1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Pierce, Elijah, circa 1967-1994 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Piwinski, Carl Bruno, circa 1994 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Polhamus, Melissa, circa 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Powers, Stephen, circa 1967-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Ratto, John, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Rice, Roger, circa 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Roberg, Robert, circa 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
    - Rodia, Simon (Sam), circa 1959-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Rogers, Sulton, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Romain, Max, circa 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Rosebrook, Rodney ("Rod"), circa 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Rowe, Nellie Mae, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ruley, Ellis, circa 1957-1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Saholt, Richard, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Samuels, O. L., circa 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Scott, Lorenzo, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Serl, Jon, circa 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - ShaEla'ReEl, Xmeah, circa 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 16-18)
    - Sharlhorne, Welmon, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Singleton, Herbert, circa 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Isaac, circa 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Mary T., circa 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Stephenson, Q.J., circa 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Stewart, Wesley, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Stoss, John, circa 1977-1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Strickland, David, circa 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Taplet, Alfred ("Big Al"), circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Tarver, Willie, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Thomas, Reverend L. T. ("Thunderbolt"), circa 1985-1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Todd, Carter, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Tolliver, Annie, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Tolliver, Charles, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Tolliver, Mose, circa 1981-1991 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Travers, Phillip, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Traylor, Bill, circa 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
    - Walker, Inez Nathaniel, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Walters, Hubert, circa 1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Warmack, Gregory ("Mr. Imagination"), circa 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Watson, Willard ("Texas Kid"), circa 1983-1996 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Wellborn, Annie G., circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - West, Myrtice, circa 1952-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - White, Willie, circa 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Willeto, Charlie, circa 1975-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Chuck ("Artist Chuckie"), circa 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Lorraine, circa 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Winkelman, Jane ("in vain"), circa 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Young, Purvis, circa 1988-1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Zeldis, David, circa 1987-1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Zeldis, Malcah, circa 1987-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - The Saint Makers: Contemporary Santeras y Santeros, circa 1988-1999; 1.4
    - Alarid, Frank, circa 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Bimonte, Fernando, circa 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Carrillo, Charlie, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Cash, Marie Romero, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Cordova, James, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Esquibel, José Raul, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Flores, Cruz, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Goler, Gustavo Victor, circa 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Herrera, Nicholas, circa 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 21-23)
    - Jaramillo, Rubel U., circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Jones, Anita Romero, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - López, Félix A., circa 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - López, Krissa Maria and Joseph A., circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - López, Peter, circa 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - López, Ramón José, circa 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - López, Raymond (Ray), circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Lucero, David Nabor, circa 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Lucero, Frankie Nazario and José, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Lujan, Ernie R., circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Lujan, Jerome, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Lujan, Luisito, circa 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Martinez, Jacob, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Mondragon, Margarito R., circa 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Ortega, Eulogio and Zoraida, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Otero, Alcario, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Pino (de Goler), Bernadette, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Robles-Shaw, Catherine, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Santistevan, Carlos A., circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Sena, Arlene Ciseneros, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Serna, Jacobo de la, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Tapia, Luis Eligio, circa 1988-1998 (Box 9, Folder 45-46)
    - Trujillo, Leroy L., circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Withers, Malcolm, circa 1997 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Loans To Exhibitions, circa 1991-1997; Series 2; (Box 10; 0.4 linear ft.)
  - American Visionary Art Museum, Baltimore, Maryland, circa 1991-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Cedar Rapids Museum of Art, Contemporary Art of the Navajo Nation (August 2-December 31, 1994), circa 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - Museums of Abeline, Abeline, Texas, Contemporary American Folk Art (January 16-March 26, 1993), circa 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - circa 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Museum Loans, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Files, circa 1969-2003; Series 3; (Boxes 10-12; 2.0 linear ft.)
  - Application material for museum and galleries, circa 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - Auf der Heide, Ralph, circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Blagdon, Emery, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Book reviews, circa 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Catalogues and magazines of work, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 14-16)
  - Cooper, Richard P., circa 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondences with miscellaneous artists, circa 1991-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Crawford, Reece, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Creative Growth Art Center, circa 1987-1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Denver Trip, circa 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Dissertation: In the Hand of the Holy Spirit: The Art of J.B. Murray, By: Mary Shaw Graham Padgelek, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Earlier art, circa 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Finn, Marvin, circa 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Freeman, Elliot, circa 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Frolich, Mike, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gallery and museum announcements, circa 1989-1999 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - Halozan, Bertha, circa 1973-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hoffman, Albert, circa 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Joy Moos Gallery, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Knapp, Rollin, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Koczy, Rosemary, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lakes, Diana, circa 1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Leon Loard Gallery of Fine Arts, circa 1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous artists not used in book, circa 1977-1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondences, circa 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Nash, Carl, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - National Institute of Art and Disabilities, circa 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - New artists, circa 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    (Kay Ameche, Berkeley J. Browne, Dorethey Gorham, Joe Hrovat, and others)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
  - Ott, Edward B., circa 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Pickle, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Publicity, circa 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - "Recent Exhibition", circa 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Saint Louis Show- Craft Alliance (1987), circa 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Santos and Retablos, circa 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Talpazan, Lonel, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Thal, Ben, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Vanity Novelty Garden, circa 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Willis, Wesley, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Wince, Charles, circa 1984-1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Unsorted files, circa 1969-1997; undated (Box 11, Folder 34-38)
  - Unsorted files, circa 1969-2003 (Box 12, Folder 1-8)
- Audiotaped Interview of Artists, circa 1990s; Series 4; (Box 12-13; 1.5 linear ft.)
  - Antonio, Johnson (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Archuleta, Leroy and Felipe (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ashby, Steven (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Basowski and Goodpaster, Denzil (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dawson, William (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Deschillie, Mamie (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - B Drummers (band music from Howard Finster opening) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Doyle, Sam ("Uncle Sam") (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Farmer, Josephus (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Finster, Howard (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Fortune, D. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Godie, Lee (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Gordon, Theodore (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Shields Landon ("S. L.") (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - McKenzie, Carl and Popeye Reed (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Navajos" (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pry, Lamont Alfred ("Old Ironsides") (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rendon, Enrique (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds, Fred (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sparrow, Simon (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stinson, Lawrence (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sudduth, Jimmy Lee and Tolliver, Mose and Willliams (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Valdez, Horacio (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Webster, Derek (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Willson, C. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Zeldis, Malcah (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Photographic Material, circa 1990s; Series 5; (Boxes 13-18; 4.5 linear ft.)
  This series contains slides, photographs and negatives, primarily of artists, but also of artwork and related subjects such as "Navajo scenes."
  This series is arranged into 3 subseries:
  5.1: Slides, circa 1990s
  5.2: Photographs and Negatives, circa 1990s
  5.3: Photos and Negatives for The Saint Makers: Contemporary Santeras y Santeros, circa 1990s
  - Slides, circa 1990s; 5.1
    - Adbuljaami, John (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Adkins, Garland and Minnie and Light, Joe and Virguos, Felix (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Anderson, Stephen Warde (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Archuleta, Leroy Ramon (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Arilla, Freddy (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Arilla, Freddy and Pinto, Rosilly and Strickland, David (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Badami, Andrea (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Beer Can House, Clark Mural, and Orange Show (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Ralph and Brown, Smokey and Merrill, Mary (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Billiot, Cyril and Ivy and Taplet, Alfred ("Big Al") and White, Willie (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Blackmon, Reverend William J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Blackmon, Reverend William J. and Kane, Andy and Philpot, David and Warmack, Gregory ("Mr. Imagination") (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Boudreaux, A.J. ("Sainte-James Boudrôt") and Ferdinand, Roy Jr. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Boudreaux, A.J. and Williams, Chuckie (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bowlin, Loy A. ("Rhinestone Cowboy") (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Brito, Frank (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Butler, Edward (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Coins, Raymond and Jennings, James (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Crowell, Harold and Howell, Robert (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Crowell, Harold and Jones, Clyde (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Darmafall, Powell ("Glassman") and Hawkes,Gerald and Johnson, Anderson and Mason, John R. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Finster, Howard (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Halozen, Bertha nd Ludwiczak, Ted and Romain, Max (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Harris, Alyne and Kass, Jacob (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Harvey, Bessie and "Barker" (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Herrera, Nicholas (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hope, Alvah and Watson, Willard ('Texas Kid") and Williams, Chuckie (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Houston Flower Man (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Hunter, Reverend John ("J. L.") and Jones, Five Cent (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Hunter, Reverend John ("J.L.") and Smith, Isaac (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray (kiln) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Jacquaz, Lawrence with Nageezi trading post (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Johnson, Anderson and Polhamus, Melissa (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Lebus, Van (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Lowe, Warren and Mitchell, Reggie and Robertson, Royal (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lown, Lynn (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Lucas, Charlie (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Mackintosh, Dwight and Rosebrook, Rodney ("Rod") (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Miller, R.A. (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Navajo Scenes (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - "Perkins" and Robertson, Royal and Sudduth, Jimmy Lee (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Roberg, Robert (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Robertson, Royal (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Sahmie, Ida and Tso, Emmett and Faye (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ShaEla'ReEl, Xmeah and West, Myrtice (bible reading) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Scott, James ("J. P.") and Williams, George (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Shiprock, New Mexico and Tattoo Tammie (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Simpson, Vollis (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Simpson, Vollis and Stephenson, Q.J. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Singleton, Herbert and White, Willie (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Robert E. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sparrow, Simon (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Strickland, David (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sweetwater, Arizona (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Talpizon, Ionel (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Telefair- "Cutting Edge" Exhibition (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Turrell, Terry N. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Valdez, Horacio (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Walters, Hubert (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Warmack, Gregory ("Mr. Imagination") (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Watson, Willard ("Texas Kid") (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Photographs and Negatives, circa 1990s; 5.2
    All photographs are 8 x 10, black and white portraits taken by Chuck Rosenak, unless otherwise noted. All negatives are 35 mm unless otherwise noted.
    - List of Photograph Information (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Abduljaami, John, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Adkins, Garland, (2 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Adkins, Minnie, (2 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Adkins, Minnie and Garland (Box 15, Folder 28)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Minnie and Garland Adkins, Linvel Barker, Linvel and Lillian Barker, Minnie Black and Joe Light)
    - Anderson, John (Box 15, Folder 29)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: John Anderson and Robert Howell)
    - Anderson, Stephen Warde, (17 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Andrews, Alpha (Box 15, Folder 31)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Alpha Andrews and Annie Wellborn)
    - Antonio, Johnson (Box 15, Folder 32)
      (9 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Johnson Antonio and Mamie Deschillie; negatives: Johnson Antonio and Alice Cling)
    - Antonio, Sheila (Box 15, Folder 33)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Sheila Antonio, Jack Beasley, Dennis Pioche, and Edith Herbert John and Guy John)
    - Archuleta, Felipe Benito and Leroy Ramon, (1 photo; 1 4 x 5 negative) (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Archuleta, Leroy Ramon, (4 photos; 2 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Arilla, Freddy, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Armstrong, Zebedee ("Z. B.") (Box 15, Folder 37)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Zebedee "Z. B." Armstrong, Tuby Brown and R. A. Miller)
    - Ashby, Steven, (1 photo) (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Badami, Andrea, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Barker, Linvel (Box 15, Folder 40)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Minnie and Garland Adkins)
    - Barker, Linvel and Lillian (Box 15, Folder 41)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Minnie and Garland Adkins)
    - Barr, Arvin W., (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Bauer, Jim (Box 15, Folder 43)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Jim Bauer, Donald Patterson and unidentified; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Jim Bauer and Rodney "Rod" Rosebrook)
    - Beasley, Jack (Box 15, Folder 44)
      (7 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Sheila Antonio; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Jack Beasley, Delbert and Wilbert Buck and Dennis and Linda Hathale)
    - Beaver, Bill (Box 15, Folder 45)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Bill Beaver and Sacred Mountain; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Bill Beaver and Louise Rose Goodman)
    - Bell, Ralph (Box 15, Folder 46)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Ralph Bell, Russell "Smokey" Brown and Mary Francis Merrill)
    - Beyale, Bob, (1 photo) (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Beyale, Bob and Sandy (Box 15, Folder 48)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Bob and Sandy Beyale and Tsaya Trading Post)
    - Beyale, Sandy, (2 photos) (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Beyale, Hogan, (2 photos) (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Billiot, Ivy and Cyril (Box 15, Folder 51)
      (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Ivy and Cyril Billiot, and Alfred "Big Al" Taplet)
    - Billups, Patsy (Box 15, Folder 52)
      (1 photo, 1 contact sheet and negatives: Patsy Billups and John R. Mason)
    - Bissonnette, Larry, (2 photos) (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Black, Minnie (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Blackmon, "Prophet" William J. (Box 15, Folder 55)
      (13 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: "Prophet" William J. Blackmon, Andy Kane, David Philpot, and Gregory Warmack "Mr. Imagination")
    - Blizzard, Georgia (Box 15, Folder 56)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Georgia Blizzard, Frank Holder, Billy Ray Hussey, and Sam McMillan; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Georgia Blizzard, Hazel Kinney and Tim Lewis)
    - Bolden, Hawkins, (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Bostic, Rudolph Valentino (Box 15, Folder 58)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Rudolph Valentino Bostic, Evelyn Gibson and Sylvanus Hudson)
    - Boudreaux, A. J. ("Sainte-James Boudrôt") (Box 15, Folder 59)
      (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: A. J. "Sainte-James Boudrôt" Boudreaux, Roy Ferdinand, Jr., and Chuck "Artist Chuckie" Williams; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Warren and Sylvia Lowe)
    - Bowlin, Loy A. ("Rhinestone Cowboy") (Box 15, Folder 60)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Loy A. "Rhinestone Cowboy" Bowlin and Herbert Singleton)
    - Brown, Anthony, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Russell ("Smokey") (Box 16, Folder 2)
      (7 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Russell "Smokey" Brown and Levent Isik; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ralph Bell)
    - Brown, Tuby, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Zebedee Z. B. Armstrong) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bruno, Frank, (5 photographs; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Buck, Delbert, (3 photos) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Buck, Delbert and Emma, (2 photos) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Buck, Delbert, Emma and Wilbert (Box 16, Folder 7)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Delbert, Emma and Wilbert Buck and Elizabeth Willeto Ignacio. 8 photos; negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jack Beasley)
    - Buck, Delbert and Wilbert, (8 photos; negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jack Beasley) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Butler, Edward, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Byron, Archie (Box 16, Folder 10)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Archie Byron, Frank Pickle and Lorenzo Scott)
    - Cahill, Duke (Box 16, Folder 11)
      (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Duke Cahill, Juliet Holmes, and John Ratto)
    - Carson, L. C. (Box 16, Folder 12)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: L. C. Carson and Michael Croker)
    - Chavoya, Raymond, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Claw, Silas (Box 16, Folder 14)
      (4 photographs; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Silas Claw, Rose Williams and Susie Williams)
    - Clark, Larry, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Cling, Alice (Box 16, Folder 16)
      (3 photos; 1 photo of vessel by Cling; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Alice Cling and unidentified woman; negatives, see Antonio Johnson)
    - Coker, Jerry W., (1 photo; 1 contact sheet) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Coins, Raymond (Box 16, Folder 18)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Raymond Coins, James Harold Jennings and Mark Casey Milestone)
    - Croker, Melvin and Michael (Box 16, Folder 19)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Melvin Croker, John Robert Ellis and Evelyn Gibson)
    - Croker, Michael, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see L. C. Carson; see also Billy Ray Hussey and Michael Croker) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Crowell, Harold (Box 16, Folder 21)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Harold Crowell and Clyde Jones)
    - Cruz, Pearline, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Damon, Matilda, (5 photos) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Damon, Matilda and son Ramie Nelson, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 24)